Long,
long ago,
there were no
boys or girls.
There were no
mothers or fathers.
There was no earth
with rivers and trees.
No one was there,
but God.@@@
God has always been.
God will always be.
There is God the Father.
There is God the Son.
We call Him Jesus.
And there is
God the Holy Spirit.
There is one
God but three persons.@@@
God family is a
little like our families.
A family is one family,
but there are different
people in the family.
There is a
father and a mother.
And there are children.@@@
God made many angels to
live with Him in heaven,
and to work with Him.
He made this world
and put people in it.
God wanted angels and
people to be His friends.