No more prison for Joseph! God
had been with Joseph in Potiphar’s house.
He had been with
him in the prison.
Now God was with Joseph
as he worked for the king.
He had workmen
build big storehouses.
Then he bought
grain from the farmers.
Storehouse after storehouse was filled.
He was getting ready for
the bad years to come.@@@
Joseph got married.
He was very happy
in his home in Egypt.
Soon he had two
little boys of his own.
He taught the boys
about the God of heaven.
He told them all the stories he had heard from
his father and grandfather when he was a little boy.@@@
The people in
Egypt loved Joseph.
He was kind to them
and told them about his God.
After seven good
years had passed,
the famine came.
No rain fell.
The fruit trees were dying.
There was no
grass for the animals.
The people ate all the
food they had at home.
Then they went to Pharaoh.
“Go to Joseph,
” he said.
Joseph opened the storehouses and
began selling food to the people.